This is where your brother used to play.
你的兄弟以前會在這里玩
You used to push him on the swings.
你以前會推他蕩秋千
Your parents don't remember him, but you do.
你的父母不記得他 但你記得
How do you know about Daniel?
你怎么知道丹尼爾的事
Will you come with me?
你愿意跟我來嗎
Hello, Jay.
你好 杰伊
Who are you? Where's my brother?
你是誰  我的兄弟呢
I'm sorry.
抱歉
There's nothing we can do for the ones they've already found.
已經被他們找到的人 我們也無計可施
They? Who are they?
他們‥他們是誰
The people your brother tried to warn you about.
你的兄弟想警告你提防的人
The people that took him away.
帶走他的人
What they do, it doesn't work on all of us.
他們做的事 不是對我們所有人都管用
We need to go.
我們得走了
You've been asking questions. Your behavior's become problematic.
你開始質疑事情 你的行為出現問題
They will notice, if they haven't already.
他們會發現的 可能已經發現了
I don't know how much time you have unless you come with us.
我不知道你還剩多少時間 除非你跟我們走
Slow down. Blend in. People are looking at us.
慢下來 融入群眾 大家在看我們
What's happening?
怎么了
They're coming.
他們要來了
Don't move.
別動
No!
不要
Run!
快跑
Go!
快走
We'll be here for a day or two, 'til it's safe to move on.
我們在這里待個兩天 等到能夠安全上路
Hey, everyone.
各位
This is Jay.
這是杰伊
- Hi. - Hi.
-嗨 -嗨
Let's get you a sleeping bag.
幫你找個睡袋吧
It's hard, I know.
我知道這不好受
There's some things we can't fix, much as we want to.
有些事情我們無法補救 即便我們很想
Hi.
嗨
You were so brave today.
你今天好勇敢
You reminded me of your father.
讓我想起你父親
He really would've been proud.
他一定會很欣慰
It's almost time.
時間快到了
Okay. Go.
好 去吧
Tell him I love him.
告訴他我愛他
Okay?
好嗎
Hey.
嘿
You wanna say hi to my dad?
想跟我爸爸打招呼嗎
Where's your dad?
你爸爸在哪里
He had to leave to go help fight.
他得去幫忙戰斗
But he promised to come back.
但他答應過會回來
Dad, this is Frankie, do you copy?
爸爸 我是法蘭琪 你收到嗎
We brought in a new outlier today.
我們今天帶回來一個離群者
I like him already.
我已經喜歡他了
I always wanted a brother.
我一直想要個哥哥
- Hey! - Don't call me that.
-嘿 -別那樣叫我
I'm not your brother.
我不是你哥哥
There's no point in leaving these messages.
留這種訊息沒有意義
Your dad is gone.
你爸爸已經不在了
Just like my real brother is.
就跟我真正的兄弟一樣
Dad, are you out there?
爸爸 你在嗎
Approaching base.
接近基地
Don't try anything.
別輕舉妄動
Why would I?
我何必
We both want the same thing, to rebuild her.
我們的目標一樣 要重建她
That's why you're taking me to your camp, yes?
所以你才帶我到你的營地 不是嗎
You think you know a lot, don't you?
你自以為懂很多 是吧
About you?
懂你嗎
I never quite know what you'll do next.
我一直不太能掌握你的下一步
But the place you're taking me, yes, I know that place.
但你要帶我去的地方‥沒錯 我知道那里
Caleb.
凱勒
Wake up.
醒醒
Where the hell am I now?
我現在在哪里
Playing another one of your games?
又在玩你的游戲
Where is my daughter?
我的女兒呢
Your daughter... like a broken record.
你的女兒‥講話一直跳針
You're not the only one who's lost someone, Caleb.
不是只有你失去親人 凱勒
Besides, why should I tell you anything when you won't tell me?
而且‥你不告訴我 我又何必告訴你
Tell you what?
告訴你什么
Your kind, the outliers.
你的族類 離群者
It all started with you.
全都是從你開始的
I don't understand.
我不懂
Unlike yours, my kind is... perfect.
和你們不一樣 我的族類是完美的
Perfectly immortal. Perfectly rational.
不朽和理性都臻完美
And yet, they're making irrational choices...
但他們卻在做出不理性的選擇
Choosing mortality, staining themselves with death.
選擇有限生命 用死亡玷污自己
How are you making them do that?
你是怎么讓他們這樣做的
How the hell am I supposed to know?
我怎么會知道
Once you told me
你曾經告訴過我
that you could fight off the effects of my parasite
你能戰勝我寄生蟲的影響
because you had something that I don't have.
因為你有我沒有的東西
You knew something, even then.
你在當時就已經有所領悟
What?
是什么
I'm afraid I can't recall.
我恐怕記不得了
This doesn't have to be a one-way street.
我們的對話不一定要是單方面
I'd like to offer you some incentive.
我想提供你一點動機
You're dead, Caleb. You have been for a very long time.
你死了 凱勒 你已經死了很久
This body that I've brought your mind back into is temporary.
我將你的心智 帶回來的這個身體是暫時的
It's already failing.
它已經開始失靈
I doubt you have more than a couple increasingly painful days left.
你可能只剩下兩天 還會愈來愈痛苦
Then I'll toss you away and start all over again.
然后我會把你丟掉 再重來一次
But there is a way out...
但有解套的辦法
An end to this torture...
能終止這酷刑
if you'd just answer my question.
你只要回答我的問題就好
Maybe you'll have better luck with the next guy.
你找下一個人試試看吧
If you won't tell me, maybe your daughter will.
你不告訴我的話 也許你女兒會開口
Frankie... she's...
法蘭琪 她‥
Alive, for the moment.
目前還活著
Why are you smiling?
你為何微笑
I'm guessing she'll break a lot faster than you.
我猜她會比你快屈服
She's alive.
她還活著
My girl is alive.
我女兒活著
And you can't catch her, can you?
而你逮不到她 對吧
I wouldn't be so sure.
我可不敢肯定
I sent a visitor... her way.
我派了一個訪客去找她
Enjoy this knowledge while it lasts.
用你所剩的時間想想這件事吧
I offered you a path out, Caleb.
我給了你一條出路 凱勒
You made your choice.
你做出了選擇
You all did.
你們都是
Hey. Hey!
喂 喂
Check the relay. See if the others have called in.
檢查繼電器 看其他人有沒有回報
The answers to the questions
她的腦袋能解答
that have kept me up at night are all in her head.
讓我夜不成眠的問題
Then we'll wake her.
那我們就喚醒她
And you can ask her.
然后你能問她
We'll need some supplies first.
我們需要先補給
You seem to know a lot about this place.
你看來對這里很熟
This park shares an architect with Westworld.
這園區和西部世界 是同一個設計師所建
So?
所以呢
I used to work there.
我以前在那里工作
Careful where you step.
走路小心
This place wasn't built to last.
這地方建得不是很牢靠
What did you do at the park?
你當年在園區是做什么的
I programmed the hosts.
我設計接待員的程式
You gave the puppets strings long enough to strangle the world.
你讓機器人變得過于自主 害慘了這世界
That was never the intent.
用意從來就不是那樣
No, but it was the outcome.
不是 但結果是如此
So, that's how you were able to pick out
所以你才能辨別出
those two hosts at the diner?
餐館的接待員
You're employee of the fucking month.
你根本是本月最佳員工
Hale would've needed someone like you
海爾會需要你這樣的人
to help spread her parasite.
幫她傳播寄生蟲
Did you have anything to do with that?
你有沒有涉及這件事
No, that was after my time.
沒有 那是在我之后的事
But Delos was notorious for keeping
但迪洛斯向來
its employees as in the dark as the guests.
對員工和客人一樣隱瞞
I didn't always grasp the complexity of the problem
我當時不太明白問題的復雜度
but what I'm most concerned with now...
但我現在最關心的
is the solution.
是解決之道
Repairing Maeve's body will be relatively simple.
修復梅芙的身體還算單純
Her mind is a different matter.
但她的心智就是另一回事
Being underground for so long has corrupted her control unit.
埋在地下這么久 損毀了她的控制元件
We'll have to replace it with another one.
我們得拿另一個來替換
His will do.
他的就可以了
We've got power.
我們有電了
Cables are connected to the generator.
電線接到發電機
You think this is gonna work?
你覺得這會管用嗎
Sixty percent of the time, she'll wake up amenable to our plan.
有六成的機率 她醒來后會接受我們的計劃
The other 40%
剩下的四成
let's just say she wakes up on the wrong side of the bed.
姑且說她有起床氣吧
You ever gonna tell me
你何時會告訴我
how you came up with these predictions, Nostradamus?
你怎有這種預知能力的 大預言家
Old habit.
老習慣
Comes from years of running probabilistic algorithms.
源自多年來大量地跑機率演算法
The people who built the original park and hosts...
當年建造原始園區和接待員的人
they started first by building them in a simulation.
首先是在模擬環境中建造他們
A copy.
復制品
Charlotte Hale did the same thing.
夏洛蒂海爾做了一樣的事
Follow me.
跟我來
In the old parks
在舊園區
they used hats to collect the data.
他們用帽子收集資料
The tech inside of them was slow.
其中的技術速度很慢
Primitive by today's standards.
以如今的標準來說很原始
To assume control of the world
為了要控制全世界
Hale needed to understand minds at a much faster rate.
海爾需要以更快的速度了解心智
So, she upgraded to what?
所以她將其更新成了什么
A ubiquitous system.
一個無所不在的系統
There was one in practically every room in the park.
當初可說園區每個房間都有一個
Easily camouflaged
很容易隱藏
because it played off the most base human impulse.
因為它利用了人類最基本的沖動
Vanity.
虛榮
Through the looking glass.
透過鏡子
No.
不會吧
Take a closer look.
仔細看看
- What are you doing? - Reformatting its processor.
-你在做什么 -重新格式化處理器
It can handle large amounts of information swiftly...
它能快速處理大量資訊
which will help us speed up Maeve's data transfer.
這樣能幫我們加速 梅芙的資料傳輸
That's Maeve's mind.
那是梅芙的心智
How long is this going to take?
這要花多久時間
Too long, I'm afraid.
恐怕會太久
Your friends will be here soon.
你的朋友們很快會來
We can't let them interfere.
我們不能讓他們干預
Hey!
喂
Hey, hey.
喂 喂
Frankie is alive, okay?
法蘭琪還活著 好嗎
I have to get out.
我得逃出去
The only way out is...
唯一的出路是‥
death.
死亡
No.
不行
No! That's not good enough!
不行 我不接受
Dying is just...
死亡只是‥
the beginning.
開始
You must... burn.
你要‥燃燒
What?
什么
If you succeed, you... run.
若你成功了 就跑
If you fail, you... hide.
失敗的話 就躲起來
What are you talking about?
你在說什么
I only know...
我只知道‥
what I told me.
我告訴自己的事
You need...
你需要‥
time.
時間
C'mon, Daddy! Race ya!
快來 爸爸 跟你賽跑
I see you've decided to rejoin us.
看來你決定重新加入我們了
Welcome back to the world.
歡迎回到這世界
Am I... Now?
我在現在嗎
That's certainly the most existential question
這肯定是近期我被問過
someone's asked me recently.
最存在主義的問題
Do you know where you are?
你知道身在何處嗎
Did she come back?
她有沒有回來
My... friend?
我的‥朋友
Right.
好吧
Long shift.
值了很長的班
I ate your pudding.
我吃了你的布丁
Gotta get back to saving lives.
得回去拯救性命了
Caleb...
凱勒
even if your friend doesn't come back...
即使你朋友沒有回來
stay awake anyway?
還是要保持清醒
When my mom got sick, I had to do everything for her.
我媽媽生病時 我什么都得替她做
I washed her, fed her
我幫她洗澡 喂她
rubbed ice across her lips when she couldn't drink anymore.
在她無法喝東西后 拿冰塊擦她的嘴唇
I was careful
我很小心
because I didn't want her to feel any more pain than she had to.
因為我不想讓她受無謂的痛苦
Just like you're doing to her.
就像你在對她做的事
This part of the process requires a delicate hand.
這部分的程序需要巧手
But she's not an ordinary host, is she?
但她不是普通的接待員吧
You knew her.
你認識她
I did.
是的
The last time I saw my father, he was with her.
我最后一次見到我父親時 他就是和她在一起
And then he never came back.
然后他再也沒回來
I'm sure it would pain her greatly to hear what happened to him.
我相信她若得知你父親的下場 會極為心痛
I want to know what happened.
我想知道發生了什么事
And she doesn't know pain.
還有她不懂痛苦
None of them do.
他們都不懂
Feelings are just an affect to them...
他們的感覺只是表象
A switch that you can turn on and off.
可以撥動的開關
You can't love or lose fully when it's just a choice.
既然只是一個選擇 就無法徹底地愛或失去
So no, I don't have a soft spot for her like you apparently do.
所以我對她沒有感情 不像你對她顯然有的
Saving the world makes for strange bedfellows.
為了拯救世界 會產生奇妙的盟友
They're back.
他們回來了
Well, then our time may be up.
那我們的時間可能到了
What the hell is this?
這是干嗎
We found the weapon.
我們找到了武器
A fucking host?
一個接待員
It was bad.
很慘
We got an outlier out, Lindsay.
我們救出一個離群者 琳賽
What happened?
發生什么事
It's like they knew we were coming.
他們似乎知道我們要來
And the only way that would've happened...
唯一的解釋
is if someone was spying for the enemy.
就是有人在為敵方當間諜
Gather everyone up. Time to find answers.
召集所有人 該來找出答案了
Don't bother.
省省吧
There's your mole.
內賊就在這里
He's a host.
他是接待員
Which makes two.
那就有兩個了
Easy.
冷靜
- What is this? - A scan. Of me.
－這是什么  －對我的掃瞄
The park was designed to collect data from guests.
園區的設計 是為了搜集客人的資料
He's trying to copy all of us.
他想復制我們所有人
You are?
真的嗎
It's complicated.
這很復雜
You have to trust me.
你得信任我
I do.
我是信你
I trust that you're lying to me.
信你在騙我
To all of us.
騙我們全部人
Get them outta here!
帶他們出去
Where's this host's control unit?
這接待員的控制元件呢
We can't destroy it yet.
我們還不能摧毀它
- Why not? - It has information about my father.
－為何 －當中有關于我父親的資訊
Once I have that, we can kill all of them.
一旦我得手 就可以殺光他們
Okay.
好
Everyone out. Get ready to evacuate.
所有人出去 準備撤離
If these two found us, more might be coming.
既然這兩個找到了我們 那可能有更多要來
The unkindest cut of all. We came here to help you.
真不領情 我們是來幫你們的
Bullshit.
才怪
You came here for your own reasons.
你來這里自有原因
And now mine takes priority.
現在要以我為主了
I need to know what happened to my father.
我要知道我父親發生了什么事
You've killed me many times. It doesn't change the outcome.
你殺過我很多次了 不會改變結果
How 'bout I kill your friend. That change anything?
那我殺了你朋友呢  會改變什么嗎
Right now, you need to focus on your friends.
現在你得注意你的朋友們
Oh, yeah, why is that?
是嗎 為什么
One of them isn't who they claim to be.
他們其中一人隱瞞了身份
- One of them will betray you. - Bullshit.
－有一個人會背叛你們 －胡說
Listen to him.
聽他的吧
He's usually right about this stuff.
他的預測往往是對的
Really annoying but right.
很欠揍但準確
Fuck you. Who?
去你的 是誰
I've run all the possible iterations.
我跑過所有可能的變化
I wish I could tell you.
我若能告訴你就好了
Sometimes, it's your girlfriend, Odina.
有時候是你女友歐迪娜
Sometimes it's Jay or Lindsay.
有時候是杰伊或琳賽
Hell, one time it was even Stubbs.
還有一次居然是史塔伯
What? Don't look at me.
什么 別看我
The mole is still out there, C.
內賊還在潛伏 Ｃ
Your team went into the heart of Hale's city
你的團隊進入海爾的城市中心
but one of them didn't come back.
但有一個人沒回來
- Shut the fuck up. - I know this is hard to hear
－給我閉嘴 －我知道這很難接受
but there's not a single version
但所有可能性中
where all of you make it out of here alive.
沒有一個是你們全部生還的
So, what do you suggest that I do?
那你建議我怎么做
You're going to have to kill one of them.
你必須殺了他們其中一人
Or they will kill you.
否則他們會殺了你
I have to go.
我得走了
I know.
我知道
I thought I could trust him.
我以為能信任他
He told you what you wanted to hear.
他和你說你想聽的話
It's a hard thing to resist.
這很難抵抗
Did you find out what his plan is?
你查出他的計劃了嗎
Just more riddles.
只是更多的謎題
At least he can't do any more damage.
至少他不能再造成更多傷害了
I don't know, C.
我不知道 Ｃ
I think there's something more going on.
我認為還有內情
I'm not sure the two of them are the only ones here we can't trust.
我不確定 這里不能信任的只有他們兩個
You think one of us was turned?
你認為我們有人被轉化了
Turned, parasited, I don't know.
轉化 被寄生 我不知道
But we were scattered out there. It could've happened any time.
但我們在那里分散了 隨時都可能發生
And what do we know about this new outlier?
而且我們對這離群者 又知道多少
Maybe she was bait from the start.
也許她本來就是個誘餌
Right now, you're the only one I can trust.
現在我能信任的只有你
You weren't on that mission. Plus...
你沒出那次任務
you never just tell me what I wanna hear.
而且你從來不會只說我想聽的話
So what do we do?
那我們怎么辦
Keep this situation on lockdown.
狀況先繼續保密
Leave me to worry about Lindsay and the others.
琳賽和其他人交給我
You do a sweep of our defenses. Meet here when you're done.
你去視查一下防線 結束后來這里碰頭
Okay.
好
Where are you going in such a hurry?
你這么急著要去哪兒
You following me?
你在跟蹤我
No, I was looking for you.
沒有 我在找你
You okay?
你還好嗎
I'm just on edge.
我只是在提高警覺
Jay ordered me to double check the perimeter.
杰伊要我再檢查一次防線
Look, baby, what's going on?
寶貝 怎么了
You're not acting like yourself.
你變得怪怪的
And I come back to find you rebuilding that thing in there.
而且我回來后 發現你在重建里面那東西
What were you thinking?
你在想什么
You wouldn't have to ask me why she was important.
你不會問我她為何重要
Not if you knew me.
要是你懂我的話
I know you well enough to know
我對你夠了解了
you're not out here checking our perimeter.
所以知道 你來這里不是在檢查防線
You're gonna go finish rebuilding her.
你要繼續把她重建完成
So, where'd you hide this host brain of hers?
你把她的腦藏在哪里
What the fuck are you doing?
你在做什么
Just move.
走就對了
- You think I'm one of them? - Maybe.
－你以為我是內賊 －也許
Maybe you're under their control. You might not even know it.
也許你受到他們控制 你也不會知道
I'm sorry.
對不起
If you're not one of them, you'll be safer here anyway.
若你不是內賊 在這里也比較安全
He's still on the run, but he won't get far.
他還在逃亡 但他逃不遠的
These humans.
這些人類
Their petty defiances.
他們可悲的抵抗
Everything they do is so small, it's exhausting.
他們做的所有事都好渺小 讓人精疲力竭
You spend your days in the city.
你平常都待在城市
I do.
是的
Do they ever...
他們會不會‥
get under your skin?
惹惱你
I don't get close to the outliers.
我不會接近離群者
I prefer the sheep.
我喜歡羊群
I'd like to put an end to this.
我想了結這件事
Shit!
可惡
Don't.
不要
Hey, Frankie's alive.
法蘭琪還活著
Frankie. I have to...
法蘭琪 我得‥
I have to get out of here.
我得逃出這里
I need to reach her.
我得找到她
Use me.
用我
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
對不起‥
Hey, hey, Frankie, slow down! Wait for me.
法蘭琪 慢一點 等我
Daddy!
爸爸
Hey! You okay?
你沒事吧
Let me see that knee.
我看看你的膝蓋
It's your very first battle scar.
這是你的第一個戰斗傷疤
You want to try walking on it?
你想試著走看看嗎
It's impossible.
怎么可能
Hey. Nothing is impossible.
沒有事是不可能的
You know what kind of person can't be beat?
你知道哪種人不會被打敗嗎
The kind that doesn't give up.
不放棄的那種人
All right?
好嗎
There you go, baby.
好了 寶貝
There you go.
好了
I met her.
我遇過她
Did you know that?
你知道嗎
When I was a kid.
在我小時候
I had almost forgotten her face
我都快忘了她的臉
but never forgot what she took from me.
但我從來沒忘記她奪走的東西
C, I know why you want to wake her up
Ｃ 我知道你為何想喚醒她
but it's too risky.
但這太冒險了
We have no idea what they were planning with her.
我們不知道他們打算拿她做什么
She could kill us all the second she opens her eyes.
她一睜開眼就可能殺光我們
I still send him messages... My dad.
我還是會傳送訊息給我爸
On the radio, to our old frequency.
用無線電傳話到我們的舊頻率
And I know that it is crazy to think that he hears them
我知道以為他會聽到 根本就是瘋了
but if there is any chance that he's alive...
但只要他有一點生還的可能
I need to know.
我就得知道
I don't want you to get hurt, C.
我不想要你受傷 Ｃ
All this will do is rip open an old wound.
這一切只會揭開舊傷疤
She can't bring him back.
她無法帶你爸回來
We have to destroy her control unit
我們得摧毀她的控制元件
before Hale uses her to take us out.
免得海爾利用她除掉我們
And if your dad's out there, we'll find him another way.
要是你爸還活著 我們會有別的辦法找到他
Together.
一起
You're my family, C.
你是我的家人 Ｃ
You're like a sister to me.
你就像我的妹妹
I can't lose you.
我不能失去你
Bernard put her pearl downstairs.
伯納把她的控制元件放在樓下
Come on.
來吧
I'm sorry.
抱歉 我知道這很難
I know this is hard but we can't take the risk.
但我們不能冒險
I know.
我知道
Jay could be a dick, but at least he was honest.
杰伊可能很欠揍 但至少他誠實
He never wanted to be my brother.
他從來不想當我的哥哥
Poor little C.
可憐的小家伙
Always whining about your fucking family.
總是在哭訴你家人的事
It's pathetic.
可悲
I don't wanna kill you, C.
我不想殺你 Ｃ
This is good news, C.
這是好消息 Ｃ
Maeve doesn't know anything about your dad, but I do.
梅芙不知道你爸的事 但我知道
Show me where her pearl is
告訴我她的控制元件在哪里
and I'll tell you anything you want.
我就告訴你想知道的一切
Don't bother with the negotiation.
甭談判了
Everything you say is bullshit.
你說的話都不能信
Cookie.
小餅干
Frankie. Hey.
法蘭琪
It's your dad.
我是你爸爸
I know you're out there.
我知道你在
And if you're hearing this, I want you to know that...
如果你聽見了 我要你知道
you're going to win.
你會贏的
You're going to do what I couldn't...
你會做到我做不到的事
because you are strong.
因為你很堅強
So much stronger than me.
比我堅強太多了
This world...
這世界
This world she... she made is... it's a lie.
她創造的這世界是個謊言
It's not real.
不是真的
But what you... what you have...
但你擁有的‥
What you have is... is real.
但你擁有的是真的
I'm sorry that I failed...
抱歉我失敗了
That I haven't been there for you...
抱歉我沒能陪伴你
That now it has to be you.
抱歉你得承擔這一切
But you can do this.
但你辦得到
You're my warrior.
你是我的戰士
I love you.
我愛你
Cookie.
小餅干
Frankie. Hey.
法蘭琪
It's your dad.
我是你爸爸
I know you're out there.
我知道你在
And if you're hearing this, I want you to know that...
如果你聽見了 我要你知道
Dad
爸
you're going to win.
你會贏的
Tell me where her pearl is.
告訴我她的控制元件在哪里
Fuck you. I took it.
去你的 我拿去
I stashed it.
藏起來了
Where?
在哪里
Behind you.
你背后
Caleb...
凱勒‥
I heard.
我聽到了
Alive.
他活著
You're his...
你是‥
His daughter.
他女兒
Of course you are.
當然了
What a disappointment.
真令人失望
I've waited such a long time to know what you had to tell your daughter.
我等了好久 想知道你要跟女兒說什么
You...
你‥
Hundreds of times, I sat through your stupid memories
我耐著性子等你回憶了幾百次
hoping to catch a single clue as to what makes you so special
希望能找到你特別之處的線索
so resistant to my command.
能如此抗拒我的命令
And I learned jack shit.
結果我啥都沒發現
So, I thought...
所以我就想
nothing like a little hope to get you to show your cards.
給你點希望 想必能讓你亮底牌
You made it farther than any of the others
你比其他人都走得更遠
and all you did was waste your shot on a worthless apology.
結果你只是浪費機會 做無謂的道歉
You think a few words will make up
你以為說幾句話就能彌補
for the choices you made all those years ago?
你多年前做的選擇
It doesn't matter.
不重要
It's done.
訊息送出了
She didn't hear it.
她沒聽到
She doesn't need to.
她不需要聽到
You're still going to lose.
你還是會輸
We didn't infect your hosts.
我們沒有感染你的接待員
You don't say.
可不是嘛
Who did?
是誰
You.
你
Your hosts would rather die
你的接待員
than live in your world.
寧死也不要活在你的世界
They're not infected.
他們沒有被感染
They're just trying to get away from you.
只是想逃離你
When I left...
我離開時
I thought I was giving him a chance.
以為是在給他一個機會
I didn't think it would lead to all this.
我沒想到會導致這一切
Part of me blamed you.
我心里一部分在怪罪你
And part of me knew that if there was any chance he was alive
一部分知道要是他還活著
it was because you were with him.
也是因為你在他身邊
Everything you guys did...
你們所做的一切
that's why we're here.
是我們在這里的原因
Well then...
那么‥
let's finish what we started.
我們來把自己起頭的事做完吧
Caleb.
凱勒
Wake up.
醒醒